onbuy.com 2019-12-19

# Privacy Policy

## 1 Who Are We?

1.1 We are OnBuy, a trading name of Visor Commerce Ltd. We own and operate this website (the "Site"). Visor Commerce Ltd. is a company registered in England and Wales under company number 09108414 and with its registered office at Unit J7, The Fulcrum, Vantage Way, Poole, BH12 4NU.

Please contact us if you have any questions or feedback about this privacy and cookies policy ("Policy") via our [contact us](https://www.onbuy.com/gb/contact/) page.

1.2 We are registered with the Information Commissioner's Register of Data Controllers under number ZA455438.

## 2 What Is This Policy For?

2.1 The Policy set out below explains how we manage your personal data (i.e. information about any identified or identifiable living person) that we collect, or you provide to us when you use or access the Site. Please read on to find out what kinds of personal data we collect, how we use and protect it, to whom we disclose it, how you can access and rectify it and how we use cookies on the Site.

2.2 Please do not use the Site unless you are completely happy with this Policy. If you do use the Site, we will assume that you do accept it.

## 3 Changes To This Policy 

3.1 We may amend this Policy from time to time when deemed necessary. We will notify you of any changes by updating this page with the new Policy, so we advise that you periodically review this Policy for any changes.

We will assume you agree to the Policy or revised versions of the Policy if you use the Site after the effective date shown at the top of the Policy.

## 4 What Personal Or Other Data Do We Collect?

4.1 We collect and store the information which you give us - such as your name, address, email address, phone number and so on - when creating an OnBuy account, via forms on the Site or when communicating with us by email or in some other way.

4.2 We may receive and store certain information automatically when you interact with us. Examples include the internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet, connection information such as browser type and version, information about your mobile or other device including device type and device identifier, operating system and platform, a unique reference number linked to the data you enter on our system, login details, clickstream data, details of your activity on the Site with date/time stamps including the pages you visited, searches you made and goods purchased.

## 5 Cookie Policy

5.1 We and/or third parties use cookies and other tracking technologies on our website. A cookie is an identifier (a small file of letters and numbers) that is sent to your computer. Our website's functionality will be limited if you configure your browser to reject cookies.

5.2 Cookies are widely used to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the website owner or others. Session cookies are temporary cookies that remain in the cookie file of your browser only until your browser is closed. They allow websites to link your actions during a browser session. Persistent cookies stay in the cookie file of your browser for longer (though how long will depend on the lifetime of the specific cookie). For further information on cookies, including how to use your browser to block them and how to delete cookies already stored on your device, visit: [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

5.3 Cookies are used on this Site for the following purposes:

5.3.1 Session cookies: We use session cookies to enable the Site to keep track of your movement from page to page and store your selections so you do not get asked repeatedly for the same information. These cookies allow you to proceed through many pages of the website quickly and easily without having to authenticate or reprocess each new area you visit. For example, the session cookie remembers your shopping basket selection so will have the items you selected when you are ready to check out.

5.3.2 Google cookies: Persistent cookies (up to four years we believe) are set in connection with the following Google services on our site and these cookies may involve certain non-personally identifying information being sent to Google:

5.3.2.1 Google Analytics ("GA"): We use cookies to recognise and count the number of Site visitors as well as providing other information about the visit such as duration, route through the website and what sites the visitor came from. This information helps us to improve the way the Site works, for example by making sure users find what they need easily.

5.3.3 Social media cookies: We may use various social media and other third-party features on our website including like button from [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/help/cookies/), follow button from [Twitter](https://twitter.com/privacy)), Plus +1 button from [Google](https://www.google.com/policies/), Pin It button from [Pinterest](https://about.pinterest.com/en/cookie-policy), share / follow button from [LinkedIn](https://www.linkedin.com/legal/cookie-policy), embed button from [YouTube](https://www.youtube.com/static?template=privacy_guidelines), These features may involve the relevant companies using cookies or linking your visit with cookies previously placed by them on your computer in order for them to collect information relating to your visit to our website or your interaction with their services or otherwise. Click the links shown above for further information about the specific features and those companies' cookie / privacy practices generally as well as to opt out where this is possible.

5.3.4 Cookie-warning cookie: This cookie takes note of whether you are happy to accept cookies on this Site based on your response to the message which appeared when you first visited the Site. This persistent cookie will remember your preference.

5.4 By continuing to use the Site, having seen our cookie notice, we assume that you consent to use of the cookies outlined above.

## 6 How Do We Use Your Personal Data?

6.1 We use your personal data to provide our services, e.g. send service messages, process payments and/or fulfil orders.

6.2 We use your personal data to help us communicate with you effectively should you try to contact us via the Site.

6.3 If you have given permission on the Site, we may use your personal data to send you emails (or other communications such as mail, phone or SMS) with details of our or third party goods or services which may be of interest to you including information about special offers or promotions. 

6.4 We may use personal data to recognize you when you visit or return to the Site to track anonymised traffic and usage patterns, to prevent or detect fraud or abuses or to help us improve the Site. We may use cookies to do this. See above for details of how we use cookies.

6.5 We retain personal data from closed accounts in order to comply with legal obligations, enforce our terms and conditions, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations and take other actions as permitted by law.

6.6 We may access, remove, alter, store or otherwise use any personal data if we have reason to believe that it breaches our terms and conditions, or that such steps are necessary to protect us or others, or that a criminal act has been committed, or if we are required to do so by law or appropriate authority.

## 7 How Do We Protect Personal Data?

7.1 Security is a high priority for us. We take appropriate precautions to protect personal data.

7.2 Email and other electronic communications are not secure if they have not been encrypted. Your communications will pass through a number of network nodes before they reach us. So we do not accept responsibility for any unauthorised access to or loss of personal data that stems from a cause beyond our control. Nor can we be held responsible for the actions or omissions of other users or third parties who may misuse your personal data which they collect from the Site.

## 8 To Whom Do We Disclose Personal Data?

8.1 Payment details including credit card numbers are supplied direct to our payment partner mentioned on our website. We do not receive such information. To ensure your details are not being used without consent, your personal data may be supplied by our payment partners to relevant third parties including credit reference and fraud prevention agencies, who may keep a record of that information.

8.2 We may allow access to your personal data by third parties who supply us with a service. Examples include e-Commerce platform providers, couriers (to enable delivery of goods), website hosts, content delivery networks and businesses which assist us in undertaking communications or monitoring our Site.

8.3 We may disclose personal data so far as reasonably necessary:

8.3.1 if we have reason to believe that it breaches our terms and conditions, or that such steps are necessary to protect us or others, or that a criminal act has been committed, or if there has been a complaint about content posted by you, or if we are required to do so by law or appropriate authority; or

8.3.2 in the case of an actual or proposed (including negotiations for a) sale or merger or business combination involving all or the relevant part of our business.

8.4 We may store or transfer personal data outside the European Economic Area (EEA) for the purposes stated in this policy. If so, we will comply with the applicable laws relating to data transfer outside the EEA.

8.5 Except as otherwise specifically included in this policy, this document addresses only the use and disclosure of information we collect from you. If you disclose your information to third parties, whether they are suppliers of services on the Site (e.g. payment providers) or other websites, different rules will apply to their use or disclosure of your information. Please check their privacy policies carefully.

## 9 Your Rights Under The Data Protection Act 2018 & GDPR

9.1 You have the right to request personal data that we hold about you, subject to us reserving the right to withhold such data to the extent permitted by law. We may charge an administration fee in line with data protection laws and we may also require appropriate evidence of identity. Note that you may be able to rectify certain aspects of your personal data within your account on our service (if applicable).

9.2 If you are located within the EU and the GDPR regulations apply to our processing of your personal data, you have the right to request the following from us:

9.2.1 Access to personal data of yours that we hold

9.2.2 That we correct or rectify any incorrect personal data that we hold

9.2.3 That we erase any personal data of yours that we hold

9.2.4 To receive your personal data provided to us

9.3 Please contact us if you believe that the EU GDPR regulations apply to you and you wish to exercise your rights under GDPR. Please note that we might ask you to verify your identity before responding to requests.

9.4 You also have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our use and collection of your personal information. For more information, please contact the relevant data protection authority in your area. 

9.5 For further information about your rights under UK data protection laws, see the website of the [UK Information Commissioner](https://ico.org.uk/).

## 10 Third-Party Sites

10.1 The Site may contain links to other websites operated by third-parties. Please be aware that this Policy only applies to the personal information that OnBuy collect through the Site. OnBuy cannot be held responsible for personal information that third parties might store, collect or use throughout their website. Please ensure you read the privacy policy of every website you visit carefully.

_Last Modified: 14th August 2019_
